[{"answer": "I have no idea how to respond to that.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "How do you feel about that analogy?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Do you genuinely believe you could become the nominee?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Time and history help change your views.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "I suppose what I would say to you about is it can be a stick to beat you with in the sense that if you never change your mind about anything, is that in itself healthy?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Yes, and it gets interrupted sometimes in the campaign.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Do you have a regime on the campaign?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "So, what do you do exercise-wise when you have time?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Not overly strict.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "I mean, do you have a strict regime on that?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "I think that's a big issue.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "And if the answer is no, is that one of the fundamental problems that the work ethic has evolved over the years?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Yes, but it's a lot more compassionate than the way, you know, it might sound.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Was that basically how you feel?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Yes, really because if you see the extent of total socialism, it's not very compassionate.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Is it, though?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Well, I think the basic principle is wrong in that you don't have a right to somebody else's life or money.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "What is wrong with that as a principle, an ambition to aspire to?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "What do they do?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "You have to understand the difference between interventionist economy and a socialist economy.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Under your presidency, what would they do to get health care?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I wouldn't give him too much credit.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Or how would you summarize your feelings?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "Well, let me read you this quote.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Can I answer that?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "To me, it's more important to admit the truth.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Isn't it a better thing that the more credible position for Republicans to say, is to say, I am encouraged by this, but he should have gone further?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "And it just sounded awful, that, didn't it, for somebody aiming to be president to talk about the poor in that way?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "If that's your number one priority, if you listen to what I have been talking about and understood free market economics, you would say the most important thing you can do is give them a sound currency, limited government, free markets, contract rights.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Would they be yours?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, let him pay.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What is wrong with that?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "It destroys the economy if you just --", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "What is wrong with having a tax system which just taxes people like him more?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "-- you got to have a president who prioritizes the poor, haven't you?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Oh, especially if it works.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Even if it works?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, justified plus legal --", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "How many of them do you believe were justified?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, from a constitutional viewpoint I don't want to fight any wars that aren't declared.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "But how many of the major conflicts have been legitimate?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "I did, but that's to go after only those responsible for 9/11.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Do you support the conflict in Afghanistan?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "To go after al Qaeda, it was like going after criminals.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "But it was war, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Yes, to a degree because it was limited.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Was it constitutional?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "There is no evidence to that.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Wouldn't they?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Well, I go and look to the rules.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "If Iran was to strike back at Israel, what would you do?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Well, the one thing that we should set aside is there's our CIA and the Mossad.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "If you believe Iran had enough enriched uranium to genuinely launch a nuclear attack against Israel, would that knowledge alone mean you would countenance military action?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "You wouldn't ever countenance any preemptive strike?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Well, let me touch your first subject first.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "If you were president of the Second World War, and you had been given knowledge the Japanese were planning Pearl Harbor, you would have preemptively struck, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "I'm trying to defend honesty.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "You're not seriously defending Ahmadinejad, are you?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Imminent attack -- if we're sitting here and we see the planes come over, obviously, yes.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "I come back to that question I put to you: if you had knowledge and you were president when Pearl Harbor happened, if you had pre-knowledge of that happening, would you have attacked?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Because I think that they would, if they could, consider attacking Israel.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "But aren't there times when you have to be the policeman of the world?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "It is not.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "I -- I am totally neutral on the cause of liberty when people want to be married and call it a marriage, it's none of my business.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "What's your honest opinion about gay marriage?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "But you witnessed this?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "But that clearly scarred you.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "I walked out of the room and thought, wow, what did I just see?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "But if they were, would you honestly look at them in the eye and say they had to have that child if they were impregnated?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "It is absolutely in limbo, because an hour after intercourse or a day afterwards, there is no legal or medical problem.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "You would allow them to abort the baby?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Life does begin at conception.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Life doesn't begin at conception?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "See, I don't see the inconsistency because I see the nine- pound baby that's still within the mother as deserving some protection, too.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Finally on this point, do you accept there is a slight contradiction between a candidate who is pro liberty, pro personal choice, pro personal responsibility in almost every other area, but on the specific area says no, you don't have choice?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Eighteen.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "How many grandchildren?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Five.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "How many great grandchildren?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "I think a lot is respect and acceptance of both of our shortcomings.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "What's the secret to a long lasting marriage, do you think?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "She'd probably be pretty generous, you know.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "If Carol was here, what would she say your shortcomings are?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Well, I can get upset.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "If you were being self- critical?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Were you a spanker when you were young?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, as long as they're not practicing severe child abuse.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Do you believe parents should still have that right to give their kids a little tap?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I think it's hard work.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "We discussed hard work, but what else?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "I think it is.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "Or do you think that's what the American dream, at its purest, is about?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "Super Bowl, haven't paid much attention to it.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Giants or Patriots, Super Bowl?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "I think it's very important.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "How important is it that you perform well in Nevada?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "I'm not thinking in those terms because I'm thinking in campaigning where the next stop is.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "ORGAN: But Nothing will stop you before the convention?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Well, it would be a real challenge, but I think people change their minds.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "Or are you implacably opposed to doing that just on principle?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "I found that if you have a good idea and you do it with love, a lot of people want to help you.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "What does it feel like to start with one person and then slowly start to build the organization?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "IM: Her name is Christine.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "What was your sister's name?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "The clinic we have in Achei, in the tsunami zone, that one is really safe.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "What kind of an impact do you think this will have?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "Some days I don't have money, but I always have support.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "I mean, in those dark days when -- when you don't have money and when you don't have support?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "I'm a Buffalo Bills fan.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "Giants or Patriots, Wolf?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "All right, I'm standing next to John King, OK, so I have to say the Patriots.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "Gloria?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "Neither.", "docId": "120203pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "Giants or Patriots?", "qSentId": 719}]